[screaming sound] this this that
look that look that look that look hey shut up
sir has come
why are you making so much noise
oh sir it's my birthday today
why are you so happy
if you are happy then be happy why are you making a big deal
oh sir today is my birthday
so what did you shoot what favour did you do to this
world by being born and what is your
contribution in this you are making noise,
disturbing people, disturbing people's sleep
oh sir stop this lecture, I will give you
some cake too.
Hey, where did you go?
Where did you disappear, sir?  Where did he go?
Come on, come on.  Cut the cake.  [screaming sound]
Wait, wait, wait, wait.  Where
is Gotiya?
Hey sir, he is not picking up our call.
Wait, I will call him now.
Who?
Hey, I am talking to you Dhoni sir.  Today is Chiku
's birthday, so we all are
going to the water park together.  That too the biggest one.  You
come to school quickly.  I don't know, my
family is very strict.  I am not allowed to go out of the house.
If anyone in my family comes to
know that I should go out of the house,
they will kill me.   Turn it off.
[screaming sound]
Shut up,
buddy.  Then shut up [screaming sound].
Yes sir.  Let us go.
You idiot.
So guys, today we are going to the
biggest water park in Indore because today is Chiku's
birthday.  So party on my side.  Hey
sir, will we go to school like this in school clothes
?
Hey, get ready quickly and come.  Go.   Okay, let
me get ready and come.
And sir, the food is also from your side, right?
Oh yes yes
this
but one second.
No, we saw it done.
Hey friend, I don't have that much money.
What should I do now?  How will I feed the children
?
What should I do friend?  Where will I get so much money from?
Hey friends, Dhoni sir does
n't have enough money to throw a party.
What?
And if I say this to sir, he will feel
bad.
Let's do one thing, we will eat food at home and go with a
full stomach and then we will
eat something light there.  Due to which Dhoni sir's
money will also be saved.
Yes, come on, come on.
[Music]
Say this Jai, watch my channel, open it and
say Jai Mata Di, follow my channel,
you will get good results, bye, like my song,
like my video [Music] Don't move my video, don't go
anywhere without commenting, don't move my video, don't
go anywhere without commenting.
Let's see, it will be fun.
Heera son, you are sitting at home swinging on the swing and
your father has come to the swimming pool.
[Music]
So finally we enter the
biggest water park in the world.  Oh my God.
Seeing so many slides makes our heads spin.
Even if it is morning till night,
we will cover all the slides
for you.
Let's get started.
I have to go to my home.  No, otherwise
here our Badri's groom, while
chilling in the water, first picked up the jug and
threw it.  [screaming sound]
Hey brother,
what do you say helicopter helicopter?   It
seems Chhappan will kill while flying in the air.
Here a different fight is going on between Gotiya and Gore Sir.
So guys, you are having fun.
Good sir.
So guys right now I'm going to flip fifty six.
See you
are fine.
Goodbye.  [laughs]
So guys, did you enjoy it?   Hey, it's
Chiku Chhabri's turn.
Hey,
now tell me what should I do?  How are you in this country
?
And here you can see guys, our car
is running the fastest and Badri is
taking Raja at such a speed and Raja is
not even falling, guys.
What is the matter, sir.
What is happening brother?   It
seems Badri will kill Raja only after torturing him.
And look brother, finally the king has fallen.
Now Badri is also trying.  Let's see whether
Badri can do it or not.  So far everything is
going well.  And Badri is maintaining a good balance.
And what is happening?  Badri also
fell.
Hey, is Chiku really that heavy?
[MUSIC]
[SCREAMING]
No, no, no, let
me go.  [laughter] Let me go.
My mother is waiting for me.   He is
lying.
Chuna
[laughs]
why are you making the video, your brother,
why are you making the video,
hey run away,
look how happy Badwa is,
hey are you moving away or will you eat the wild man's flower,
see, he will eat the wild man's flower to his heart's content, he is jealous,
oh [ __ ] friend, no, this is not Dalpari, this is Dalpara.
This is a corpse.  Hey, it's a corpse.
[screaming]
So guys, we're going to go to the biggest
slide right now.  Look how big this slide is.   It's going to be a
lot of fun and I'm also feeling scared.
And only four people can go in this slide.
Jagchi is not allowed inside this slide.
We are very excited.  Let's see
what happens.  The slide is at a very high altitude.
Now we will have to walk.  So guys,
wait now what will happen.  Wow
[screaming]
beautiful.
So guys, there is so much crowd but
come up to the top floor.  I also don't know,
look this is the seventh or eighth floor.
Oh my god.
Hey friend, I am worried.  It's been so long now,
look down there is a line all the way down.
Good.  Oh my god, the line is so long.
Oh [ __ ], man.
When will the number come?  It's also getting late.
Good sir.   It is about to be time.  It will
not be possible.
Come on brother.
But the time has come.  Get Let's Go.
[screaming sound]
Hey, I'm having fun, basically.
Oh brother, what fun it is.  Hey, look at
Sumit's face.  Everyone is feeling very scared.
[screaming sound]
Look how happy he is.
Our parents know, do whatever you want.
Send it to the police.  To the police.
Mom also knows.  His father also knows.
So finally we have a smooth landing.
So tell me guys how did you like this slide of ours.
So guys, now we're going to go to this slide
and see what
reaction we get.  I am very scared guys.  Let go.
So first of all I took it to
Gotiya Dada.
Now you are gone son.  Now you are gone and see.
So now it is Dhoni sir's turn.  Hey, start the car.
What is it?  His hairstyle became like that of a rooster.
[screaming]
[music]
So now it's Chhappan and Badri's turn.  This madam will
just press one button and Chhappan will go straight into the
underworld.
End.   Oh no no guys,
I was just joking.  The
name of this light is Capsule.  Here
Chhappan is a little scary because
not everyone can go inside it.
Went.
And this is our Badri Bhaiya.   It
is very hot.
[laughter]
[screaming]
Guys, how much of a crown.  There
is so much crowd.  Look at this.
Look, look, guys.  Look, oh
my God, so much water, we're going to go
over the slide.  Let's see, it's going to be a lot of fun.  Let's
see from where we will
fight the storm and the helicopter will come and save us.
Look guys, Badri is in such a hurry to
leave.  It seems as if we are
climbing the stairs of the temple.
Hey hey, where did this water come from?   This is what happens
here.   Let's go
upstairs and see what reaction we get.
So Guy's making an entry through the Jag slide.
We are all going to slide together
and
we have kept the mobile at risk for you.  So don't let the video
stop you from liking, sharing and subscribing.
got it.   Let's
go to the top, guys.
What speaks above all?
Get up.   I
swear on my mother.
We all entered inside the same slide.  It seems
everyone is going to be hit with a stick
from behind.  Whoever is sitting in front will not be hit.
This is the first place in the Gotiya.   Let's
see who gets a good welcome.
Brother, I was sitting in the flight but it became a
kicking and punching machine and I got so many kicks from behind, guys.
[Music]
So guys, we're about to go on a
big ship, here it is.  And there's a storm on this ship,
guys.  So now we are going to go in this ship.
Look, water is also coming from above.
So let's quickly climb up.  Come on, come on.
[MUSIC]
So it's called a ship's wheel.  Which is used to
handle the ship.  Hey, but there's a
big storm coming here, guys.  Hey, a
big boundary has come.  Move out.  Come, come,
save it from drowning.
Or hold it and drive it.
What kind of people live here, friend?
So guys, our boat is stuck here.  So
we are getting it out somehow.
What did America say?  What are you?
Today we ask, what are you?   I will
fix it right now guys.
After coming out of the storm, we started playing
Holi and that too with such a big water gun.
Do you also want this squirt gun?
But for that you will have to come to the water park.
So guys, the water there is very deep, like the
ocean, so let me go swimming there.
Come on [screaming sound]
So guys, I'm the world's largest
mermaid.
Guys look Jalpara,
what are you having to see all this?
Save me Dhoni sir, save me.
Hey, stop the drama.   I survived.
Hey
hey why are you coming back?
So guys, how crowded is it?  Look at this.
What has happened?
I am going to go inside it now.
And its name is Wave Pool.  Waves emanating from it.
People were picked up and thrown down.
So let's dance a little now.
This Badri is dancing while holding Chhappan.
[Music]
My heart remembers you every moment
[Music] My
love.
So friends, you can see how many
people there are and how much crowd there is here.
As soon as this dance ended, we tried to
get into the water.
Hey, where have everyone gone?  No one is visible.   Do
n't do this my love.
And Jagga also did scuba diving here.
depression.
He has gone crazy, Baba.
So guys, some kids were
troubling us a lot.  You were saying that
you are a YouTuber.  You are a YouTuber.  To whom did we
say yes?  So we said no, we are not YouTubers.
Ok.
Oh my God.  He started making noise here also.
etc.
Wow wow wow wow wow wow wow
good son you are lucky
darling
[Music]
What did America say, if
I don't tell you then
brother you will have to ask why is he getting angry,
who is
Baba Tillu
[Music] Oh my God
[Music]
anything
[Music] He was a man of a different level.   I
enjoyed it and I
want to give this enjoyment to every person in India.  Let us go.
We all finished bathing but we
saw that some special people were dancing here.
[MUSIC]
[CHEEKING SOUND] So guys, it's evening.
Now we are going to leave from here.
Hey, you must have understood.
What is this?
Let's change now guys.  I have had enough
fun.
Good.
Now it seems like stomach worship.
Come on brother.   Come here
Alia.  Son, don't run away.
[screaming sound]
Hey, it will be fun.
So what will you guys eat?  make order.
Sir, please just order a sandwich for us.
Ok.  Waiter
ji, please say sir.
Bring them a sandwich.
And something for you too?
[Music]
For me, it's pizza, burgers, Manchurian,
noodles.  And yes,
bring the best or most expensive thali here.  Go.
Ok sir.  I enjoyed it brother.  Had fun.
This
[laughter]
[screaming sound]
because I can't curse.
No, don't abuse.
Family sees family.  Otherwise, if I abuse you like this
, if I abuse you like this, you will
remember it for the rest of your life when you grow up.
We will show, we will do this, we will do that, we
will do this, we will do that.  Look how happy he is
becoming.
Khacha Khacha Khacha
Hey guys, otherwise
we are ending this vlog here.  I
hope you enjoyed this vlog a lot.
Why has Chiku come
or not?
I had a lot of fun and it was my first
time going to a water park.
And yes friends, please do tell us in the comments where
we should go next.
So guys till then like this video
, comment and subscribe to the channel.  Bye.
[screaming]
[music]